Syed Haseeb

+923463600128

haseebumerzai@gmail.com

I am a Software Engineering graduate with exceptional development qualities. I come up with sound knowledge of Android Applications development. Along with that, I have wide-ranging experience in Web, Windows Apps, Cloud computing, Virtualization and Linux Environment





Experience

04/2023 to Present

Android Developer

JanBark Technologies, Islamabad Pakistan

- In-house development
- Architecture and Design Pattern

10/2022 to 04/2023

Android Developer

NINESOL Technologies, Islamabad Pakistan

- Product based development
- KOTLIN, MVVM, KOIN

08/2022 to 10/2022

Android Developer

ITEAS Technologies, Islamabad Pakistan

- Product based development KOTLIN
- Ads Integration (AdMob Facebook)

01/2021 to 03/2021

Android Developer

Softech Universe, Rawalpindi Pakistan

- Developing Android Apps JAVA
- Ads Implementation

08/2021 to 10/2021

Asp.Net Developer (Internee)

PTCL HQ, Islamabad Pakistan

- Delivering different tasks related to Web
- Developing Web sites using ASP.NET
- Networking and Software Installation

10/2019 to Present

Android Developer Freelancing

Fiverr, Local Projects

Highlights

- KOTLIN
- JAVA
- RFACT
- XML
- SQLITE
- ROOM
- FIREBASE
- ASP.NET
- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- BASH
- BAT
- DART
- JSON
- C
- C++
- C#
- LINUX

Education

BSSE (Software Engineering)

2018 - 2022

Shaheed Zulfiqar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology, Islamabad

Android Development Certification

2019

Sina Institute of technology Islamabad

Languages

English, Urdu, Chinese (Beginner)